<root><loc><x>39.868202</x><y>-75.386639</y><desc>Free scrap (Upland)Free scrap, oven, little heater etc. DO NOT REPLY if you can't get it. Located in Upland in delaware county. No scammers all scammers will be reported.</desc></loc><loc><x>40.029323</x><y>-75.040569</y><desc>Navy blue carpet squaresNavy blue carpet squares I think 12x12 they are the big ones never used just been sitting piled up in basement  Like 50 of them</desc></loc><loc><x>39.982776</x><y>-75.825508</y><desc>6 ' full size truck cap (caln)cant tell you much about it, friend had an 8 foot bed on his truck and he was using this for awhile, he just got the correct 8 foot cap and he left the 6 foot one here, must go , looks like the back window lift works ok , rained today so its a little [...]</desc></loc><loc><x>39.872545</x><y>-75.288652</y><desc>Free kids long six drawer dresser *curb alert* (Delco)Free kids long bureau. Cream color with wood top and flower design. One of the drawers is off track but could probably be fixed. Also missing one knob. It's outside covered with plastic.  Please leave the plastic.  Free if you want it. Must pick up.  [...]</desc></loc><loc><x>40.186800</x><y>-75.007100</y><desc>player piano, bucks county (holland)in nice condition,was restored once,but needs work,can help you pick up in your truck call wayne   &lt;a href="/fb/phi/zip/5115425449" class="showcontact" title="click to show contact info"&gt;show contact info&lt;/a&gt; </desc></loc><loc><x>40.045200</x><y>-75.422700</y><desc>Konica Minolta /Color Printer (Devon)Konica Minolta /Color Printer Free</desc></loc><AddressString><addr>%3A+%31%30%35+Nicholas+Dr+Hatfield+PA+US</addr><desc>Kitchen table and six chairs (Hilltown)Curb side pickup. Free</desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+%31%37%32%32+green+street+Philadelphia+PA+US</addr><desc>Free wooden bed frame (1722 green street)Curb alert free wood bed with all pieces. In good condition minor scratches and wear queen size</desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+%33%31+Miami+rd+norristown+PA+US</addr><desc>above ground pool, chairs, vanity (30 Miami rd)Free to pick up. Our trash day is tomorrow so tonight's the night </desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+Eagle+Stream+Drive+at+Prince+Drive+Eagleville+PA+US</addr><desc>Curb alert: couch and chaise loungeFree couch and chaise lounge.  Left by previous resident; Chaise has two loose legs.  At curb at 51 Prince Drive, Eagleville, PA</desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+Market+Street+at+%38th+Street+Philadelphia+PA+US</addr><desc>Foot stool (Center City)Free IKEA foot stool. Overall good condition. Can be used with recliner or swivel chair. Pick up tonight or tomorrow morning, as we are moving out tomorrow! </desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+%35%32+Fawn+Drive+Southampton+PA+US</addr><desc>Free BricksApproximately 50+ rectangular red bricks for free, with 1 scalloped brick and 2 broken bricks. Used, but in good condition.  Curbside at 52 Fawn Drive, Southampton PA 18966. First come, first served.</desc></AddressString><AddressString><addr>%3A+E%2E+King+St%2E+at+Ruthland+Malvern+PA+US</addr><desc>Hyland's Restful Legs &amp;amp; Restless Legs Calming Creme, Homeopathic (Malvern, PA)Someone got me these a couple months back, thinking I had restless legs syndrome / RLS, but I don't. Didn't want to go through the trouble of shipping them back to the company. Would like them to go to someone who can use them.  These are both brand  [...]</desc></AddressString></root>